No brother, Bakshi can touch Big Red 100% now,
And we need new Big Red that the dam treasure cannot give. However, as for the location of Bakshi’s treasure chest,
It’s actually cloudier than the dam! Xiaopu,
I worked all night to find the locations of these twelve treasure chests for everyone. Everyone should collect them first.
Don't be like Xiao Pu and get confused when you find it. The first treasure chest is in the corner next to the weapon chest on the third floor rooftop;
The second treasure chest is in this gap under the small shed in the camp. It is dark and completely invisible;
The third treasure chest is hidden under the stool that goes to the bag throwing box;
The fourth treasure box is behind the box on the main road; the fifth treasure box is not at the circled position on the map at all.
But next to the pile of clothes in the snow, do you know how long I have been looking for it?
The sixth treasure chest is behind this scrap car next to the train. The seventh treasure chest is in the Bloodsucker Platform corridor.
The next scene is even more exciting, and the money hidden is even more underworld. Brothers, you must look carefully at treasure chests No. 8 to 12.
Treasure Box No. 8 is in the floor-to-ceiling wall area of the Batiang Tower, and it is actually hidden at the end of the corner.
It can only be touched through this seam. It's so dark, you might as well bury it.
Treasure Chest No. 9 is under the red glowing slope on the museum floor. Treasure chest No. 10 is in the toilet cubicle on the first floor of the old wall.
You have to lie down to see it. Treasure chest No. 11 is under this house that doesn’t even provide small supplies.
Treasure Chest No. 12 is on the first floor of the top floor of the Tower. Go from the hollow toward the wall and stand behind the chin.
The above is the location of all the treasure boxes in Bakshi. You must collect them.
Some points are too hidden in the west, and I was really looking for Hong Wen. I was so angry that I ran to treasure box No. 8 this afternoon.
Hiding in the west corner of the corner, squatting here to lure two bears, and then go out to get their treasure.
I got a medical robot to relieve my anger.